so if everyone came really fast here
with a very special beer tonight
now I am pissed why my
face because I was just betrayed by
someone that I had looked up to you for
so long a voice actor from Sonic
on the raft the best TV show ever and
you may wanna who the betrayed me
was it Julia why the blackout Homewood
Sonic no it was more Isla mouse the
voice actor of like Uncle Chuck and
Slade
like you know like objects are local
and sling on rope Dingos badass
about the other part of and my and
robotics be sexy too
but anyways after that like moolah mouse
was doing our guy so I thought denim I
need some of that so I looked up
online I found addressing fellow
damn he was doing all guys and you
catch him so I'll meet thee Wed dug up
so my old Slee John and send it up for
that life for that tips I'm
thinking damn I'm gonna get back in the
car Mons like nobody else gonna have
this because I'm a true su fan like I
even told him in the letter that I'm his
none more passive famine cuz sweet
sexy and although I'd
never got that bad marks Maurice
LaMarche what the is my like I
don't want to call you out but it's been
what five months and I still they can't
back my mama mama keeps the camera
for keep we're not doing this again I'll
keep the camera on me mama is it forward
you can edit that out if you own this
again Mitch time mom without tax again
I'm standing up for my car sleek sexy
cutting out for my car sleek sexy movie
seminars it's been five months we'll the
is my chair I haven't been this mad
since I was like walking down the
walking through target and I punch them
all so I'm fine and
you
like like I saw baby are they stuff and
all the people where's mine where's
my anyways I don't even know I'm
gonna call this video like moist moist
moist all my I don't know like I
don't make a but in the title so
I'll just say like what some I was like
rough to you see started an autograph or
some like yet anyways like comment
subscribe do all that peace